So welcome everybody to the webinar.
Yes, you can reverse your chronic
diseases and this is for you to learn
some of the basics and understand
how it works. So many of you will have
been told that
there's nothing you can do. Chronic
diseases are called chronic because they
are forever and all you can do is manage
and they will get a little worse. And
but you know you just take your
medicine, you take your pills and do
your treatments and um that's it. That's
all you can do.
And I'm sure that
you have been told this
perception or this perspective of the
medical industry.
Now, how come I can just say yes, you
can?
We want to look at that and we want to
see if we can get you kicked off in the
right direction.
And I have many ways to help you
get going and get to the best possible
body you can have. A little bit about
me. I just got back from a little run,
just a couple of miles. I'm 73 years
old. I'm still a little flushed in the
face from my run, but that's what we can
do. And there's no ache, there's no
pain, there's no pills. So my goal is to
remain painfree and pillf free for the
rest of my glorious years, right? And I
think there could be many
if I don't get run over by a truck. So,
how am I so confident that
it can be done?
Well, there's always a story, right?
There's always an experience that kicks
us into
gear, so to speak. In my case, I was
born with a hole in my heart and I was
always sick as a kid. And you know, you
just make the best you can of what you
have. And but because I was always
curious, I always lived with, oh well,
I'm just weaker and sicker than others.
That's just what it is, but I'll make
the best of it anyway.
But then
at 50 years old,
I had a stroke
and that was
kind of like a death experience. Any of
you have had those
where you're like, "Oops,
looks like it could be over." Right? and
you're kind of out of the body and you
kind of think, "Oh, this is what it is.
It's it's over. It's done."
And then some of us have had the
experience that, oh, you can actually
yell at yourself and say, "No, it's not
over. I want to get back into that body.
I want to get back into life. I in my
case, I had young children. And I had my
children late at 40 and 42. So at 50
they were still kids.
So they needed me.
And in that moment,
there was this realization.
Oh my god, I know that it can be done. I
know that there's a lifestyle that gets
me to
totally good health in spite of this
heart issue, in spite of the fact that
we are not born perfect, right? Nobody
is.
Well, some people think they are, but
[laughter] you know, it may not be the
case.
Um,
so I researched and learned and studied
and experimented, but I already knew
that there's one way that guarantees
the best
nutrientdense diet and the best
environment that we can give ourselves
and exercise and air and breathing.
So
I put myself into my own program that I
developed. Now there's one other thing I
want to say about that.
There were already some people working
with raw food. Victoria Bhutenko I was
reading and meeting and studying
um for example
and there were others but their food was
often so bland I really didn't like it.
So I was a foodie. So I said I can do
this and make things tasty.
Any of you foodies?
Any of you love delicious?
So let us combine the joyfulness, the
fun of getting healthy with the
joyfulness of having tasty food and a
vibrant life.
So,
of course, then I developed a program
for clients and studied with people from
whom I learned how to run an online
business and learned
to put a structure to
how you get your disease reversed.
And there's some beautiful, beautiful
client stories of mine. I'll just give
you a couple
um one I love very very much because it
was just so surprising even to me.
Um, I had met a a gentleman, a
filmmaker,
um, online
because he was recommended to me as a
brilliant
mind with insight into how the world
runs and all of that. And he was on one
of my summits.
And one day he called me and said,
"John, I need you."
The doctor told me, "I'm going to kill
over and not come back."
And I picked him up. He was a a state
over. He was going to stay in my guest
room and do an in-house
recovery.
He couldn't sleep more than 20 minutes
at a time because his diabetes was so
bad and his kidney failure that he had
to go to the bathroom every 20 minutes.
He couldn't walk because there was so
much water in his legs. I mean, he
walked on a cane like labor step by
step. His back was in constant pain
because of arthritic um elements that
were the result of a spinal injury years
before.
So there was rheumatoid
arthritis in his joints as well and he
was about 100 pound overweight.
So
he came to my house.
I put him on my program
and four days later, four days,
it still boggles my mind. He said, "I
want to do a testimonial." So he set up
his camera and you know all set. He's a
filmmaker, right? So,
and he tells me that that testimonial
exists. He tells me, you know, just 4
days in, he has slept a couple of hours
at a time. He's been walking up and down
stairs. He's been walking around the
block very slowly
um and with help.
and he just feels like and he's already
lost in 4 days 10 lbs. Of course, a lot
of that is water. When you're that much
overweight and your kidneys are failing,
you you're gathering a lot of water in
your legs and in your limbs. So,
10 days later, he was walking a mile.
I don't remember how many pounds he
lost.
and he was off back to Los Angeles and
continued the program remotely, lost
over 80 pounds that I think now now 100,
made beautiful movies and was just
recently won an award at the Can Film
Festival for one of his documentaries.
So, I love that story because it's so
extreme.
And of course, there were hundreds of
other stories that were much milder
where somebody has
diabetes and the value comes down to
normal in 10 days. Where somebody has
arthritis and the pain goes away, takes
a little bit longer, three, four weeks.
And
why is that?
How come all these statistics and I want
to show you some statistics
are so
extreme
and we just blindly believe that America
is the best the most modern medicine. It
has it all. right,
has great longevity.
And then we see how people live over 50.
And I want to show you some statistics.
Um, actually, I'm going to start with
the incredible cost
of being sick.
Now, a lot of that
we don't see when we are in a regular
insurance. When I was working
um for corporate America, so to speak,
even in the '9s, I was already paying
1,500 a month for me and my two small
children. I never used it because I
already didn't go to doctors
um in the early 2000s I should say
rather than 90s
and
we are drained by this system not only
physically because we're ailing but also
financially because we're submitting to
there's no other way and you have to
take this medication and had one client
recently who said, "Yeah, you know, I'm
still on this medication. It costs me
$450 a month just for this one pill."
And that was her co-pay.
So,
yeah, let me show you a couple of
statistics.
Um,
I think here's the cost.
Yeah, for individuals over 50, the
average health care cost ranges from
8,000 to over 15,000 per year. Then it
goes up 50 to 54.
Um,
oh wait, so I guess the the first
statistic is for everything, right? It
starts 50 to 54 with 6,000 to 9,000.
Then we get to okay I'm going to share
my screen so that you can see what I'm
reading here. This is just what AI shows
us.
See here in the beginning was the
overall
then we see age 50 to 54 is somewhere
between 6 and 9,000. Ages 55 to 65 we're
looking at 8,000 to 13,000.
And then it just keeps going up. And
look at this.
Total retirement estimates, financial
planning should should plan for
$170 to $300,000.
You can buy a house with that.
and you're spending that on staying
sick.
I'm sure many of you woke up one morning
and thought, I just don't want to live
like this. There must be another way.
That's probably why you're listening to
this.
There must be another way.
So
we can quickly look at what are these
chronic diseases. Right now we are
looking at
76% of adults all adults from 21 years
up
report having at least one chronic
illness.
That's
34 of our population
are sick.
Think about that.
And then we get to the age factor again.
over 65,
93%
of Americans have at least one chronic
diagnosis
and are obviously then on medication,
right?
Of course, many many have multiple
children are now at 30%.
So what are all those diseases? heart
disease.
Let's look at the heart for a minute.
Now again, I can talk. I have a heart
that is defective,
[laughter]
but it is still a muscle and a muscle
can be trained and when fed right, it
can be rejuvenated
and that little hole will never go away.
But the rest of the heart can be so
strong that the little hole doesn't
really matter.
So that's also something we need to
realize. When we cut off our finger, it
will never grow back. But the rest of
the hand can become so agile and so
capable that it doesn't matter.
I'm sure you've seen those
um situations where people just relearn.
Um so
obesity we're at 40%.
Of course, overweight, we're at over
70%.
Um, diabetes,
they don't even give us the percentage
we
numbers are so great.
But diabetes and pre-diabetes, we're
also at almost 60% now. So,
what is the main what are the main
causes?
And even AI today acknowledges that it
is lifestyle.
See here the the main risk factors.
Tobacco use is still up there. I can't
believe that there are still people that
smoke cigarettes, but there are. So, and
the second item is poor nutrition and
lack of physical movement.
They call it here physical inactivity,
right? So, lack of physical exercise
and then there is alcohol
and let's just throw alcohol in with all
the other
recreational drugs that people may be
using
and you have it.
So, I just wanted to show you that that
you are not alone
obviously
and this is the number I want to hone in
on. the 93%.
Now, I want to know who of you wants to
be in this 7% when you get over 65.
Maybe you're already there. I'm already
there
and I'm having the best time of my life.
So, if you want to be in the 7%,
do me a favor
and connect and I'll teach you how. So,
I'll teach you a little bit now, but I
want you to remember you want to be in
that 7%.
Isn't that insane? There's only 17% of
people who are actually healthy at over
65.
So you want to be in that 7% and you
want to be one of the participants who
expand that 7% into more.
All right,
enough of statistics.
But even I am always shocked when I see
these numbers
like I had never really looked at the
cost right at the enormous cost of being
sick because even if you are insured you
have the co-pays and you have the drug
co-pays and you have the not covered or
you didn't get approval from the insurer
etc. So you have all these other
co-actors
that amount to
Yeah. to to numbers that
you could buy your kid a house, you
know, instead of
paying for
drugs and medical care. Um, all right.
Let's get to
Please use the opportunity. I'm going to
Oh, I can't I can't do that. I can't.
The chat will not be visible for those
people seeing the recording. Um, I want
you to connect with me. Go to
my website to connect with me if you
want that. So, that's that's what we're
going to do instead. We're going to just
go to my website and you can connect via
the contact button there.
Let me just pull that up so you can see
it actually on screen. It's
Johannesfoods.com.
Um,
see if I can pull it up. Here it is.
And share once more.
and it has this
this
image on there that I I just like it.
Yeah, you can. You absolutely can. All
right. Here we have some testimonials.
Also, when you go to the website, these
are recent clients. Oh, you have former
mayor of New York City, Eric Adams. He's
not very favorite anymore, but when I
interviewed him, he told me the story of
how he
um got himself out of severe diabetes
and neuropathy and almost blindness
and then he did become the the mayor. So
that was a good part. Then he got sucked
into all the wrong things when he was a
mayor. But that's what happens often to
politicians, right? So,
um, yeah, Ali is not on here, the
filmmaker.
I still have to put that together, um,
or put a put a written one together to
put it on here. So, you go to
Johannesfoods.com
and find the contact us button, right?
And then you can connect with me.
So
just to let you know that you can always
find me. You can also Google Prof
Johanna Sophia or Professor Johanna
Sophia and you will find all kinds of um
information about me. But now to
why does it work?
How does it work?
Couple of questions.
When you look at
nature, just look at the trees and the
plants and the animals and the insects
and all of nature.
How does nature
nourish itself?
What kind of nourishment
do they all consume?
Different kinds of course. insects. I
mean, bees eat eat nectar from from
flowers, right? And
deer eat grass and
elephants eat big leaves and, you know,
entire trees
and
all the other animals eat all kinds of
food that is according to their species.
And then I always ask, well, how do they
eat their food? In what state do they
eat their food? And the answer is always
everybody can come to that answer by
themselves.
All living things
nourish themselves with other living
entities, other living things, we could
say. Right? So all of nature feeds
itself with raw food.
Period.
So if you think that this here, this
part, this skin, this body is also part
of biology,
which of course it is,
then this biology needs the same
nourishment that everything else needs
to rejuvenate itself, to renew itself,
to fix everything.
We may all have learned that cell
reproduction continues throughout
any kind of life cycle, right? In your
why my skin is shiny and and
fresh is because it literally
rejuvenates itself. Especially when we
also exercise. Like I told you, I was
just running and
you sweat and you sweat out stuff that
the body doesn't need. And you inhale
via your skin cores. For example,
especially if you run under trees, which
is what I do, you know, in the woods, um
you inhale
live
energy and actually bacteria etc. from
the air around you, especially when
there is other natural elements around
you. So, and
if I want to be really well and really
healthy, I consume living foods,
which means
you got the answer. I don't need to tell
you, right? And if I don't have enough
of living food, my body starts to fall
apart. Now, why does everybody fall
apart somewhere else?
Because we all are born with weak spots.
Why does one person get arthritis, the
other person gets diabetes, the next
person gets liver failure, the next
person gets kidney failure, the next
person gets heart disease and strokes,
and the next person gets
arthritis. I already said migraines and
autoimmune diseases and so many other
diagnosis.
because
the body fails where the weak spots are.
Like if I weren't training my heart,
that would probably be the place where
there would be more failure.
>> So think about it. Where are your weak
spots? Where do you need to give your
body
extra energy to replenish, to fix, to
reorganize, to rebuild the cell tissue
around the body? For example, you're
told that cartilage never renews, right?
And it may not be exactly like it was
when you were 20, but yes, it does
rebuild.
You got to try it to Some people need to
try it to believe it or need to do it to
believe it. And
what else can you say about the biology
in
your world? When we look around to me,
that's the basis for everything.
Yes, we have cultures and we have all
kinds of um help with our lifestyle so
that for example we sit in chairs, we
don't crouch and we um we have cars so
we don't need to walk long distances or
ride on horses
etc etc. So there's a lot of wonderful
technology that we have invented but at
the same time we have neglected the fact
that our biology needs extra
energy
to handle all that technology.
Especially now with this additional
electromagnetic
field energy that is yeah that is kind
of heavily impacting our own energetic
field.
So
is it all about just
a thing in your diet that can fix it?
Like many people come to me and they
say, "Well, I'm I'm already taking
turmeric and ginger and
yeah, I think it's working a little but
not really. Why is it not working?"
Because no one remedy can override the
rest of your lifestyle.
And like we said, these are all
lifestyle diseases.
only a change of lifestyle can reverse
them.
Make sense?
So,
while we're
hoping for that special remedy,
I have to say unfortunately
that's not going to go.
And the lifestyle you need to make it
work is of course more than just a diet,
especially in the healing phase.
I was just listening to a
health coach who works with
um with a sort of a an elimination diet
approach.
And she she was saying you got to be
radical. You have to be radical. I'm not
saying you have to be radical. You just
just have to do what makes sense.
So what makes sense in terms of how
nature works, how biology works, is
living foods, and all the other
modalities that have to do with a
healthy lifestyle. What else is a
healthy lifestyle, you may ask?
Your body needs oxygen. Again,
when you walk or run under trees or in
in the fields, not in a glyphosate
field, not in a field where something
has been sprayed, right?
But in healthy nature, you will of
course get extra oxygen from the plants
around you.
Even in your house, plants will enhance
the air. We all know that. You can't see
mine because they're all on this side
where the window is where the windows
are. So,
we need good oxygen. So, we need to
learn how to breathe better.
Then we need
what else do we need for a healthy
lifestyle. We already said exercise. So,
more breathing, more oxygen.
We need exercise meaning muscle
training.
Walking is always the first thing to
start. If you're already working out,
make that workout as healthy as
possible.
Again, under trees is always better than
in a in the basement. So, what else do
we need? We need good sleep. How do we
get good sleep?
Well, how did Ali get good sleep? who
the filmmaker who
could only sleep 20 minutes at a time
by getting your organs to function
so that everything functions without
interrupting your sleep because the body
naturally wants to sleep and it will
sleep.
Um, I just finished one of my classes
and
one of the clients was saying, "Guess
what, Johanna? I slept 8 hours last
night." That hasn't happened in decades.
So,
it just happens because your body wants
to get there. You don't have to take
sleeping pills or extra um
extra anything.
other than breathing
and getting the organs, getting your
organs, getting all your functionings to
work well enough. Because of course,
that's what your body does when you
sleep, right? It fixes, it digests, it
repairs, it does all kinds of things in
your sleep. And when you deprive your
body of sleep,
Yeah. what happens? You're groggy.
You're exhausted when you wake up.
You're getting up. You want to put your
feet down and it hurts.
Ever had that experience.
So
to get rid of all of that, it is that
entire lifestyle change. There are other
elements.
There's also
the chemicals in our household. What's
what is in your household? What kind of
soaps and shampoos and deodorants and
shaving creams and hair products, etc.
are there?
Bonnie said you're just doing your hair
or dyeing your hair, right?
What are the chemicals in those products
that impact our health?
How can we exchange them for products
that are not harmful, that are not
chemically derived?
There are always those alternative
products that are supporting the biology
as opposed to harming the biology. So,
we try to exchange everything in our
household for those better options.
What have I forgotten? Oh, there's
another modality we learn.
Um, you can find versions of it on the
internet probably also. But if you work
with me, you will learn deep relaxation.
Why
deep? You know, just relax, just be
okay.
No, it's a not it's a completely
different very physical experience
working through your body. I talk people
through
um I developed that with my acting
students when I was teaching acting and
directing.
So,
what that is is you're working through
your body from your tippy toes to
eventually
the top of your head and everything lets
go. And when all your muscle tissue lets
go and all your tendons and
tensions, your nerves and everything
relaxes,
guess what happens to your mind?
Guess what happens to your worries?
They also disappear. It's a beautiful
thing. So the physical deep relaxation
leads to the mental emotional relaxation
and suddenly stress is gone and you can
put that or you can automatically feel
the smile on your face because
you love your life.
you
can function in whatever situation you
are, you will know what the next move
is.
Um
so
working on the biology to make the mind
and
the emotional side also work
has one more element and that's our
social life.
Humans are social creatures.
We
love being among other people.
are made, our species needs
a community, needs acknowledgment that
we exist
and needs physical and emotional
touch.
closeness with others.
Of course, in today's world, we have
this incredible loneliness epidemic,
especially among young men, but also
women.
The loneliness
that leads to depression and
deterioration
and a lot of suicide
because
of what I just said. Humans alone
cannot
function.
Yes, we can survive phases where we're
alone, but there's always the hope, the
vision to reconnect.
Um, one of those classical examples is
Walden, right?
Going into the woods, building
a hut for himself and collecting
mushrooms and foods and um growing a
garden. And after two years,
he realizes
I have to go back.
This is not
bliss. This is the opposite. It becomes
very oppressive.
Even if you're connecting to the animals
and to the trees and plants, we humans
need other humans to become
and experience ourselves as humans.
I had
a discussion in one of my classes
about the fact that
we don't even become humans
when we're not around humans.
There are all these examples of babies
taken out to the woods and brought up by
animals, brought up by the family of
wolves. Those are the most famous cases,
right? But also kids put into total
isolation for other reasons. There's the
Casper Hower story
and many others. And you can see
when they grow up from an early age in
isolation or with the animals, they
either become like the animals or um do
not become humans. is capable of speech
or even upright walk. They have to
painfully relearn
and often cannot reawaken that humanness
in them. So I'm telling you that because
we also need for good health.
I call it resocialization. We need that
resocialization. We need to find groups
that we can physically connect with,
meaning we actually have in-person
meetings
near our home. Um,
or go hiking with others or whatever it
may be. Or go play bingo. It's all good,
but it has to be something that you
enjoy and can share with others. Of
course, that can also be a meaningful
work. It can be service. It can be
volunteering with your church or with
your social services.
There's so many ways of reconnecting
with society and with others
in a way that enriches your life and
it's part of the healing process.
So, think about that. All of these
elements belong into that self-healing
process because while I can teach you
how that works, you have to do the work
and you have to want to be in that 7%
that we were talking about.
Is that what you want?
Now, if you're still with us, Ramona,
Bonnie, and Lewis,
um, feel free to put a question in the
chat. Of course, that was what I was
supposed to be doing,
um, answering questions in the chat, but
as Bonnie told me, it seems you didn't
even receive the link to the webinar
until the last minute. um that of course
has prevented many of the 25 people who
were registered not to show up. That's
really interesting. So let
let me hear if you let me read if you
have any questions.
If not,
um,
I just want to put the link in the chat
again where you can from here connect.
It's go.jana Johanna's
raw foods.com
slash
book a call.
If you don't have diabetes,
you can also use the link
that I'm putting now that instead of
book a call has start and then you get a
free download of my raw chocolate book.
Um,
but like I said, it's not for people who
need to first heal from diabetes.
Okay, let me do that also.
So that's that link.
So you might want to copy those and
and use them to set up a direct talk
with me.
Okay. All right. the the protein
question. I'm glad you're asking because
I thought we already had that down.
Quick question to you. Where does the
elephant get the protein? Where does the
rhinoceros get their protein? Where do
all the big apes and gorillas get their
protein?
Quick answer.
What do they eat?
leafy green stuff,
mostly green stuff,
right? They don't need to cook beans to
be the most powerful
creatures on the planet.
So, one of my colleagues, Dr. Milton
Mills, will say you you can hear him say
that in the documentary, What the
Health?
You will say, "How often do I have to
tell you all proteins are made by
plants?"
That's why they all get their protein.
And lions and wolves just get it
secondhand through the prey they consume
because their prey mostly are herbivores
that consume
those green things. I'm talking about
fruits and roots and green stuff, leaves
and stems and
grasses,
right? So, that's the protein story. And
yes, I also I also have wonderful um raw
sprouted chickpeas, sprouted lentils,
etc. Very um high density protein
plants. But even if we didn't use those,
we still get loads of protein from leafy
greens raw.
Any heating, and I didn't go into that
part of the biology, any heating above
120°,
excuse me, loses you half of your
protein value as well.
So
yes, um there's a wonderful raw hummus I
make um with sprouted chickpeas
there. Yeah, there are lots of ways you
can use sprouted lentils, sprouted mung
beans,
and
I use millet and other grains that are
very rich in protein and um other
minerals that we need. So,
so yes, there's there's a huge array of
protein sources because all living
things contain protein. And again,
all living things should feed on living
things.
Not that I want you to go and dig your
teeth into your bunny rabbit. I always
say, and eat it alive, please.
[laughter]
I mean, you could, but it it would not
be easy. You know, you you and it would
not be delicious to humans at all.
Um,
of course people have tried.
Um, yeah, thank you for that question.
And no, we don't need any soil.
Yes, you sprout the lentils.
You know, you have you ever seen how
people sprout things? Have you ever seen
sprouts in the store?
Yes, you can eat rental. Say yes.
You sprout.
You sprout the lentils.
Do you want me to explain how sprouting
works or do you want to just Google it?
Sprouting works by putting raw lentils
into water. You just so that they're
just covered with water
um overnight and then you pour off the
water and let them sit rinsing them once
a day. Not leaving them in water
anymore, but rinsing them once a day or
twice a day if you are in a very hot
climate.
Um until little roots come out and then
the first little leaves come out and
then they're delicious to eat. actually
just I mean they're delicious to eat and
soft and crunchy just when the when the
root comes out.
Do you want me to show you?
Yeah. We used to have these these chia
What did we call them?
Chia seeds on a
on a hedgehog, right? On a hedgehog. Uh,
of course not a real hedgehog.
[laughter]
On a hedgehog
made out of ceramic or something, right?
We would put chia and then then they
sprout these little um green sprouts.
Yes. Mhm.
Pumpkin seeds. I have not been able to
to sprout pumpkin seeds to tell you the
truth, but I just recently made a
delicious raw
um pumpkin seed cheese like um
yes, you can you can eat pumpkin seeds
raw. Of course, you know, they're
they're offered as snacks, right?
Just don't use the roasted ones, use the
raw ones.
Um,
yes, you see them in the stores,
especially in health food stores. If
health food stores are big enough, they
have a bulk section and then you can get
them by the pound. And it's it's
incredibly cheap protein when you think
about it, you know.
And you sprout them, you put them on
your salads, you put them on your
sandwiches, or of course, if you want to
do the real raw um healing protocol,
then your sandwich, the bread of your
sandwich would would also be raw. It
would be a dehydrated raw bread.
And of course, you know, my clients have
all the recipes for that. We need a
dehydrator.
And
yeah,
any any other questions.
So yes. Um, Louis, all
all proteins are made by plants or are
in everything living. Um, but especially
in plants.
Okay. So, you found sprouted pumpkin
seeds. Do they are they actually
sprouted or are they are they just
soaked and dried again?
because they call that sprouted, you
know, but they're not actually having a
little root and leaves growing out of
them, right?
Yeah. Mhm. Yeah. They will have those
that are
soaked and then re- dried, dehydrated.
So, and that is done so that the life
force in your seeds awakens.
All right, guys. We are we are coming up
to the finish line and I want you to
know that I'm starting a new class next
week. It starts on Monday at 1:00 p.m.
Eastern time. So, that would be
um 1000 a.m.
Pacific time. and you can figure out
everything in between.
And if you are in Europe, that will be
at 700 p.m. Central European time. I
know that a couple of European people
were signed up for this webinar. Um, but
this, of course, is a very late time for
them. So, they would be um
for for them it would have been 1:00 and
it would now be almost 2:00 a.m. for
them. All right. So, you know what to
do. You can connect either via my
website or via these these links.
um yeah that I'm going to send to
everybody also when I'm sending out the
recording of this. All right,
I look forward to seeing you soon. Um
join the next class.
There's always a way to figure out how
you can do it. But you got to decide to
really do it. Like I said earlier, you
know, you got to be radically decided to
get healthy and then you will guarantee.
Ciao. See you soon.